Hello everyone, this is our type b. Shinjuku née, we have our 5th anniversary concert.
We're going to do a random play dance using songs that Umami has participated in over the past five years.
I'm going to do a random play dance using songs I've participated in over the past five years.
I'm not saying it's a song, but it's a song.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it, though I'm really nervous about it.
If all four of us can dance, we've cleared the competition, so there are 10 songs in total, so let's try our best to clear the competition!
Buber Booth
Booth
If I can clear 10 songs...
I want to eat meat!
I want to eat it!
Let's go for it!
It's all about the meat!
It's on! I'll do my best!
Let's get on with it!
First song, please!
Oh, I got it! I did it!
I made a mistake!
Did you get it? Did you get it?
Oh, OK!
Good!
Okay, next.
I was surprised to see that the two-handed swinging is so good.
I don't do it very often.
Now let's play the second song, please.
Two hand gestures?
No, I can do it.
OK!
Phởadores.
Ho exacerbated
à
Conscious before death
eh day?
Let's go next.
Lily!
From here, let's go to perfectionism.
Okay, let's go to the third song.
Three, two, one.
I want you to like me
I want to get warmer
How's that?
There's only one hand gesture.
I think I got it because I only have one hand gesture.
Apparently, my left hand is about to snap out of my hand.
Everyone's part of each other,
I'm just saying,
I think you're doing okay.
You got a nice haircut.
Watch out for the monty.
Fourth song. Please.
There's one more.
Oh no!
A little bit, Risan,
Well, thank goodness there's only one person left.
I win!
I like you.
I might be two years old.
Maybe two years old.
Could be two.
Could be 2 years old
I only have one hand gesture for this one, too.
Wait.
But I thought it was two-handed too.
There.
Both hands there, too.
Both hands.
I wasn't doing this.
I was doing this.
On the way home today.
I'll go back and watch the video.
But I'm doing it.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no.
No. No.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't do it either.
We all are.
I'm sorry, sir.
All of you.
If you can swing it.
Yay!
You're so sweet.
Thank you very much.
All right, let's go.
Fifth song.
Please.
Ooh!
Oh!
What, 13 minutes?
Oh, wait. Oh, no.
Too perfect.
I thought it was much better, Mimi.
I knew it. Sometimes cool songs are in the headset, so...
I can go for it.
You got this one right, didn't you?
I'm getting into a good groove.
And now for the sixth song, please.
Mike, Mike, I did it.
That's not right.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Finished downhill
WOW
Probably three of us are left in three pieces.
Let's see...
This is...
It was more than I thought it would be.
That's great!
I think it's really great.
It looks good on you, that's for sure.
That's for sure.
But I didn't think there would be a pattern like this.
I see.
And now for the seventh song.
Oh, my God.
It doesn't even make a sound.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, two hands.
Two hands!
Ooh!
Ooh-ohh!
My favorite song my favorite song
Can we afford it?
Yeah.
I'm really going to eat the barbecue, are you okay with that?
Are you sure you're okay with that?
Anything is fine.
Oh, my God!
If we get through all of this...
Three more songs.
Let's go.
I think we can do it.
Last spurt, song 8, please.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ahahahaha
술 Drink, drink
Ahahaha
eler
Hahaha
Ha ha ha ha
right? Left?
He's like an old man.
I'm gonna go get some flowers.
Oh!
You did it.
Good job. Good job.
I dance too much.
I thought we were all wearing red dresses now.
Mute.
I've never done this in such a big semicircle before.
How about this?
How did it go?
I'm wearing Bambi.
Good night.
It was perfect.
Wow.
I'm so glad I waited for you.
I got a choreography lesson in the middle of the show.
Choreography?
That's about it.
Okay, you're all clear.
What?
I'm so happy.
Oh, my God.
The last two songs.
It's okay, really.
9th song, please.
Nice to meet you.
отдель quest concealed
A star wide face
I'll hurt you with me
please
Thank you, Gozaimasu Sei
It's a big calculation
You're crazy.
I've got a lot of questions.
You forgot.
Why don't you come over here and I'll tell you?
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Super Salon.
Sambar one night in a day
Love is a melody
Oh, hey.
Good! Good!
What? Did you guys just do that?
Hey! My body just started moving on its own.
But you're all like, "Oh, my God, I can't believe I'm doing this!
Yeah!
Well, how was it?
You danced great.
Oh!
What? One more song, right?
What? What?
Grilled meat hands!
Good! Good job! Good job! Good! Good!
What time do you want to meet today?
Uh, sure, after this.
The April Assaultro section is starting.
Let's dance!
I can't find my fingers.
I love this!
It's the last 10 songs! Please!
Va-va-voom!
Yeah!
That's it!
Full of it!
You gotta rinse it out!
Vaah!
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Wait!
Did I make a mistake?
Was it really a set?
Really?
You can dance like that!
I didn't think you could dance like that.
What? Can you talk?
So...
I'm going to be lenient.
I was lenient.
Actually, I just got a little bit, a little bit, a lot wrong.
I got a lot of questions right.
I danced a lot of songs!
I could dance!
I had so much fun practicing!
Ten songs!
Yes, I was so happy!
We got to dance as a unit.
I heard it's far away.
I was so surprised.
I couldn't get close enough to the camera.
Here we go... here we go...
So here we are...
The second part of our 5th anniversary project
How was everyone?
Were you able to dance?
Please look forward to the 5th year of Noepi-chan!